let questions = [
  {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Is Python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?",
      answer: "a) yes",
      options: [
        "a) yes",
        "b) no",
        "c) machine dependent",
        "d) none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "What is the maximum possible length of an identifier?",
      answer: "c) 79 characters",
      options: [
        "a) 31 characters",
        "b) 63 characters",
        "c) 79 characters",
        "d) none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Which of the following is invalid?",
      answer: "b) __a = 1",
      options: [
        "a) _a = 1",
        "b) __a = 1",
        "c) __str__ = 1",
        "d) none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which of the following is an invalid variable?",
      answer: "b) 1st_string",
      options: [
        "a) my_string_1",
        "b) 1st_string",
        "c) foo",
        "d) _"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Why are local variable names beginning with an underscore discouraged?",
      answer: "a) they are used to indicate a private variables of a class",
      options: [
        "a) they are used to indicate a private variables of a class",
        "b) they confuse the interpreter",
        "c) they are used to indicate global variables",
        "d) they slow down execution"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following is not a keyword?",
      answer: "d) pass",
      options: [
        "a) eval",
        "b) assert",
        "c) nonlocal",
        "d) pass"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "All keywords in Python are in",
      answer: "a) lower case",
      options: [
        "a) lower case",
        "b) UPPER CASE",
        "c) Capitalized",
        "d) None of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which of the following is true for variable names in Python?",
      answer: "a) unlimited length",
      options: [
        "a) unlimited length",
        "b) all private members must have leading and trailing underscores",
        "c) underscore and ampersand are the only two special characters allowed",
        "d) none of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which of the following is an invalid statement?",
      answer: "b) a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
      options: [
        "a) abc = 1,000,000",
        "b) a b c = 1000 2000 3000",
        "c) a,b,c = 1000, 2000, 3000",
        "d) a_b_c = 1,000,000"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which of the following cannot be a variable?",
      answer: "a) __init__",
      options: [
        "a) __init__",
        "b) in",
        "c) it",
        "d) on"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "Which is the correct operator for power(xy)?",
      answer: "b) X**y",
      options: [
        "a) X^y",
        "b) X**y",
        "c) X^^y",
        "d) None of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "Which one of these is floor division?",
      answer: "b) //",
      options: [
        "a) /",
        "b) //",
        "c) %",
        "d) None of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "Which of these in not a core data type?",
      answer: "d) Class",
      options: [
        "a) Lists",
        "b) Dictionary",
        "c) Tuples",
        "d) Class"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "Given a function that does not return any value, What value is thrown by default when executed in shell.",
      answer: "d) None",
      options: [
        "a) int",
        "b) bool",
        "c) void",
        "d) None"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "Following set of commands are executed in shell, what will be the output?\n>>>str=\"hello\"\n>>>str[:2]\n>>>",
      answer: "a) he",
      options: [
        "a) he",
        "b) lo",
        "c) olleh",
        "d) hello"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "Which of the following will run without errors ?",
      answer: "a) round(45.8)",
      options: [
        "a) round(45.8)",
        "b) round(6352.898,2,5)",
        "c) round()",
        "d) round(7463.123,2,1)"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "What is the return type of function id ?",
      answer: "a) int",
      options: [
        "a) int",
        "b) float",
        "c) bool",
        "d) dict"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "In python we do not specify types, it is directly interpreted by the compiler, so consider the following operation to be performed.\n>>>x = 13 ? 2\nobjective is to make sure x has a integer value, select all that apply (python 3.xx)",
      answer: "d) All of the mentioned",
      options: [
        "a) x = 13 // 2",
        "b) x = int(13 / 2)",
        "c) x = 13 % 2",
        "d) All of the mentioned"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "What error occurs when you execute?\napple = mango",
      answer: "b) NameError",
      options: [
        "a) SyntaxError",
        "b) NameError",
        "c) ValueError",
        "d) TypeError"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "In order to store values in terms of key and value we use what core data type.",
      answer: "d) dictionary",
      options: [
        "a) list",
        "b) tuple",
        "c) class",
        "d) dictionary"
      ]
    },
  ];